Like the candle hit the stream
Linners on the altar
The portal's open, no place to hide
And nobody falters
Tricks walk through the tarot spread
The magic's coming through
Transmission, yeah
That means you
Ready for your sale tonight
Beast kid, gang, come running, got the
be to come back one more time thunder at the window nancy wrote in on the rain pull the magician
manifest and defendants like his name she got time don't even know his panel box and there we go
a officer alex my queen your man smoke machine and coughs controlling drags him off the hate i
caught him in the light and who i wanted him to be not who we it's the night and tony's on the
Okay, let me get this, let me get this.
There's a new Crystalline video I've heard.
It's a must-see.
Ooh, but I'll get this first.
What's going on here?
I don't know, I don't know what he's saying.
I don't know what he's saying.
No, I'm just spying on him.
I don't know what he's saying, but he's spying on him.
I don't know what he's saying, speaking Brazilian.
Okay, okay, so let's see, okay.
Yeah, so Grapple or Grapple has a new a new crystalline video, I think so good to see you should know things for being here
Let's see
See I can find it. Let's see
It says crystalline spurging again
deleted live or
Delusional crystals ready to take down channels. Which one is it there?
Let's have a look
Latest gas lighter line crystalline spurging again. Okay, let's watch this one
Oh my god, it's Carl. She's talking to Carl. That's not good
Rachel last night. You have fun. That was fun with mini wasn't it? That was so cool
Hope he comes back soon
So here's this crystal amity. We can watch some of it. Let's see if we like it. Let's see
Here we go. Oh shit
You were a dick to me me for me me talking to me cuz she wants you know me I
Know of you
because you were a dick to Mimi for Mimi talking to me because she wanted to go
on stream with me and you're all like you should stay away from Crystal Ann
right? And actually I knew of you before that. But why would you tell Mimi to stay
away from me? Did everybody tired that? Yes.
You like was you were spurging out on her because she wanted to go on stream
And I said well go live with you if you want to stream and you're like why would you why no you need to stay away from
Crystal and I've done nothing. I don't even know you done nothing to you just because I stream
Does it mean I'm a bad person? No, I didn't say that
No, but why would you tell Mimi to stay away from me Mimi? Obviously, I'm cool with Mimi. I know I understand
I don't like beta though Big Bird sucks. Yeah. Well, that will we both agree on that
Yeah, because Big Bird lied on your name saying that you threatened to unalive yourself several times
Oh my gosh, you like they told me that you actually that wasn't your character Mimi eggs because I asked her that
because I didn't even know about you and I told Mimi if you feel like you feel like you want to
be with Carl that is your business and no one else's. And true and can I can I interject?
Mimi spent three days with me in person in January. She saw I was nothing like that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, she came to California. I didn't go to New York. Oh, yeah, you're planning on going to New York
No
I never said that
I do know that y'all met though. I do know that she came down in January. I was right saying this
Okay
When you were messaging her you did say
You wanting you wanted to see her again. Oh
What see her I'm gonna fucking marry her. You know
Yeah
Maylandz and banjoo because q45 is a dick. Of course. I want of course. I must hear again
The thing is you told me me to lay low
But here you are not laying low about y'all's really well the reason why I want to come up because uh, I know she's cool to you
She really likes you. Okay
And the reason why, because I want to do it like a public apology. Can I do that?
Oh my God.
I public apologize for all the disgusting, heinous, grotesque stuff that I said to her.
Oh.
I've never done that before. We never do that kind of relationship, you know.
Uh, something was said and I got, can I, can I, can I fish? Can I fish? Can I fish? Can I fish?
But you should be saving this energy to apologize to our kids.
I, well, no, I already did that.
But since she brought it publicly about what I had said, I'm doing it publicly here.
Anderson?
When did she do that?
When she was going on the world tour talking about what I had said.
She was sorry, not sorry, though the world tour.
The world tour.
No, you said this when you apologized to her.
No, I'm talking about initially when she came back to the community.
That's what I'm talking about.
Right, but that was okay. Can I finish? Can I finish? Can I finish what I've seen there? Please?
So I publicly apologize because I have never said any of that stuff to her before
We've been together for
over two years
Mostly on sometimes off, right? I've never said any of that stuff to her, right ever ever in my life, right?
Or let alone not just her just any woman I've ever been. Oh my god liar, but
I take full accountability for that.
But can you admit that you also went on a world tour about Mimi?
Uh, excuse me?
You went on a world tour like from panel to panel talking about Mimi and the breakup, too.
Um, when?
You went on Kate's you went on clumsy's I believe I think you went on big birds. Oh my god
Wait, wait, wait, you're gonna mixed up. It wasn't me. I never did that
You would they go on panels and stuff. No, I didn't know I didn't after that. I never did that you're gonna mixed up
It's not me
No, no, pull it up right now. I never did that
I put down my dead parents, I never did that shit.
Fuck no.
What are you talking about?
I went on a world tour for their breakup.
I went on those panels.
I was like, what are you talking about?
I was in the community.
You were kind of talking about the breakup.
I was not in the community at all.
At all.
The first time I've ever seen you on a panel was on Kate's, I believe.
No, but you're seeing, I went on, let's go back to what you said.
You said I went on a world tour talking about the breakup.
These three different, four different panels.
I didn't do that.
You're like, be careful of Mimi or whatever.
I never went on those panels and said any of that stuff.
I was not even typing in chat.
Where did you hear this? Where's the proof?
Somebody has to have clips, right?
Right, that's when Mimi broke up.
You went on Kate's panel and then like the next day, Mimi broke up.
Are you serious?
Put it on something.
That's what I saw.
You might have not talked.
I know you.
I did not go on Kate's panel after we broke up in April.
Are you serious?
I was not, I was not.
Thank you.
Yeah, you did.
Crystal in, Crystal in.
Look at me, look at me.
Right before y'all broke up, but she.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You just sit after.
I'm paying attention.
I have very good memory.
I'm listening to what you're saying.
You said after the breakup,
I went on a world tour talking about the breakup.
But it was kind of weird,
because the next day Mimi goes on the panel to defend herself.
No, I'm going back to what you said initially.
You said after the breakup,
I went on a world tour on these different panels
talking about the breakup.
I never did any of that shit.
So now you're retrying what you said?
I don't know the times. I just know y'all were, y'all were talking about it.
I never, listen, this is the first time, well actually I joined Samazard because I said my clumsy,
but this is the second panel I've joined since. I remember you going on
cake, clumsies, no, you went on cake, then you... I mean, it goes on, I mean, it's like,
here's the link if you want to check it out, and then make sure you subscribe to Grateful 2026.
That's it. Maybe Grateful 2024. I think it's Grateful 2026. Okay. Yeah, check the rest of that out. I mean,
yeah, Carl's just ridiculous. Oh, gosh, how are you guys doing? Yeah, so we had a fun
fun night last night, though. We did Mini Manson. Maybe I'll show a few clips. Actually, I wanted
to show like last year's, last year's appearance, because that was also classic. That was, you know,
Very fresh just meeting him and
Having the first conversation so we can have a look at that. Let me see video is blocked in some territory. Okay, switch account
So this is last year's mini man's interview. It was probably about
Last March or something and I have one
Well, and of course now it's not here. Of course, the videos disappeared now
So all live, okay must be one of my lives
Okay, okay fuck it was so I was like fuck this
And I'm wearing a suit and everything and I'm going in the women's bathroom
To me a bathroom is a bathroom, but I could see why women would be like
Now I'm used to Patrick's day parade and people just jumping in front of each other to pee men women
You know sheep animals
So it was like a festival spirit, so I'm like it was normal to me
I didn't we have something in common because I did see a clip of your you are a Ripley's believe it or not
Before I transitioned I was female
now son Ripley's
How's that very poor health and very overweight then but my cat was
Because I lived in St. Augustine and they filmed it after Ripley's believe it or not there
She was about a mile from where I lived.
I could walk there.
I could walk to everything when I lived in St. Augustine.
Your cat?
I lived.
Yeah, so I got to be on the show.
It was great.
And your cat was a very unique cat.
Very interesting.
Can you tell us about that cat?
She had a question mark.
She was a calico.
She had a question mark on her back
and the tip of her tail was white.
I didn't have to contort her or anything like that.
It was there, it was just naturally there.
Yeah, well I thought the tail had like a little white dot on the tail and there's the perfect
question mark on the back, you just put the tail up and it makes the dot under the question
mark.
Yeah.
I was on the front of the newspaper because the reporter just happened to show up during
lunchtime and everyone was at break.
So their state he shows up. Oh, Ripley kind of looked like that, but she had orange on one side of her face
This one this is right here. Yeah
We're both cat lovers. I love your tricks. Yeah here for animals anymore. I'm older and I just
You know, no no pets now the vet bills. That's why yeah, that's number one
Well, I have six cats and so I hear you there, you know
Tell us of you right now
Mini is jealous
Well, tell us how you got started in your character and and had had you came up with the concept and
Tell us a little bit about that. I actually only made a video once I got into Marilyn Manson
I was like, I'm not into him anymore,
but I was for like about two years.
In the first year, I was really intense about it.
Kissing on his picture, I had a picture in the door.
It's gone now, things are different now.
Billy Idol is my go-to guy and David Bowie.
But Marilyn Manson has like some style
and his showbiz personality helped me.
I made thousands of dollars off of that over the years.
especially when Marilyn Manson wasn't performing and he was still canceled.
He was canceled for four years.
So I was able to capitalize on that for all those Marilyn Manson fans who were
craving a different kind of performer because there was no other performer like him.
And that's why I still call myself Mini Manson and still were to make up,
you know, because he'll probably get canceled again and I'll take over from there.
I like his gothic image and also his views about Christianity and I learned about Satanism
and Anton Lavey because of him and that philosophy helped me to package myself better and to
take the ugly.
I mean I was always considered ugly and undesirable and Anton Lavey says, hey, you should capitalize
on that.
You should amplify that.
I was able to make an image and because I was so gung-ho about Marilyn Manson, I mean
I was really putting the blood and shit, the fake blood, and without my shirt on, but everything
and being really badass and like a real rock star on YouTube, being as fucked up as it
is and that everyone hates Susan Borchicki, sorry Susan, but a lot of people are mad at
you because you're taking away people's freedom.
You never personally done anything to me, but a lot of people are blaming her YouTube in general is they don't let me even take my shirt off
I'm afraid they'll strike me which I know just to take it off my shirt
So I'll either have a vest on or on my jacket or something
They took a lot of that the raw edge that people my fans liked about me
and tried to turn me tame so that old ladies,
you know when you got a lot of old ladies being your fan
and like, and you're doing something wrong,
my friend Joe G, who I want to promote,
he told me, he says,
you don't want a bunch of old ladies being your fan
because that will take your credibility and edge away
and he's right.
So I got rid of this one old lady who was spying on me
and trolling me for the last three,
three, four, three, four, three, four, three,
done you to her.
I'll choose my rough and ready fucked up fans who use drugs and alcohol over some fucking rich old fucking cougar
That's offended my my belly in my language. Oh my god. You shouldn't wear makeup and you don't sing so good
Maybe you should just do your art cards instead
This lady's lucky. I don't dox or she said some real bad things to me in an email
I mean, oh yeah, Christina is always saying,
oh, I'm so old, she's like, I'm an old man now.
You know, I'm, you know, first of all, I'm 45.
And so it's like, I'm not that old, but you know,
and it's like, you know, she portrays herself
like she's 50 or 51.
I think she's like, we heard she's 75 years old
or something like that.
And so, I mean, not to dogs or anything, but it's like,
you know, and be proud of your age.
I mean, it's like, I mean, there's nothing wrong with eight.
At all ages, it's experiences.
It is just a number in like so many ways.
But then to like, call me an old man and stuff like that.
Maybe I'm an old man.
I was more of an old man when I was like a little kid.
I was like, I had an old man personality.
Now I'm like, kind of like a younger personality.
But oh, there's Lola.
Oh, Lola, what are we going to do?
What are we going to do, Lola?
I just don't know.
Oh, you're just going to cuddle up there?
I don't know.
I'm like, I kind of like a little bit.
Yeah, I've been out of it for a couple weeks, you know, I was on my I was on my American flag speedo world tour last night
I am I went to good times show. I went to
LES, New York City. I went to food stamps. I I
woke up with a smile and it's just in my speedos and
Wanting to move to New York. Yeah, that's miss Lowe. Isn't she beautiful? It was a beautiful cat. You're so regal
Yeah, she's right. You're always always on guard for me, right? There's Lenore. Lenore, do you come over here too?
Lenore, Lenore is looking away. Lenore is like
Lenore, why are you looking the other way?
Pretending you don't see?
Lenore!
Hi. Oh, yeah, she's over here. It's okay. It's okay. Hi, you're on camera. Oh, she's off
Okay. Well, who knows what the kind of day would still be. I mean, it's like, if anyone wants to do, yeah, it was a Speedo tour.
I'm still wearing them. I can show you a little bit. Like, I won't show too much, but, you know,
see, I was very proud to be an American last night, and I still am today.
Oh, there you are. You like to be like when I wear Speedos in the house? Yeah. You came right back up, right? Okay.
Everybody's like, oh, your cats are your props.
No, the cats want to be on, they love the camera.
When you're gonna be on a camera, can they have a kisses?
Can they have a kisses, Lola, can they have a kisses?
We had a Speedo World Tour, it was great, it was great.
But I'm banned from Good Times show now.
And probably some other shows,
but I don't remember exactly where I was last night.
It was quite a tour though.
It was quite a whirlwind tour.
You know who I like?
I think I'm attracted to Harry Tudzikus.
I'm attracted to LES, and I'm attracted to food stamps.
Now, the funny thing is, I've never really seen
anything that they look like.
They could be like revolting people,
but just their voices reminds me of like
being on like news radio.
And I'm like, I'm like Andy Dick.
Hi, you know, and there's Joe Rogan,
who I think might wanna fuck me.
That's Harry Tudzikus.
Um, the rest of the guys I don't know. I mean it's like I've never talked about gay sex more than with these guys
I mean they're just interested. I mean it's like I don't know if they're experimenting with themselves. I mean everything is
My balls my my dick my asshole. I mean, that's what I mean. That's all they talk about
I'm gonna finger you. I want to wrestle with you. I want to
I'm gonna suck your D and you suck my D and
I mean, it's like, I've never had such a gay experience.
I didn't know straight guys were that gay.
It almost makes me rethink.
I think I might turn straight so I can be more gay.
Cause when you're gay, like they don't accept,
I can't even like, you know, make a joke.
Oh, you're cute.
Oh my gosh, this is like offensive.
And then it's like, they're like,
I want to put my big dick in your mouth, you know.
food stamps, and he's like, okay, come teabag me, you know, papa, and it's like, wow.
I mean, I've never heard people talk like this. I mean, they can teach me how to be gay, I think.
What do you think? I think they can. And if they'd like to, I'm willing. I'm willing to,
whatever they want to do to me, they can do to me. I don't know. Just leave me alive at the end of it.
And it don't stretch me out too, too much, but...
Okay, well, I guess getting a little bit I'm getting a little bit a little bit. I'm hot under the call right now
So I should I should probably go. Yeah, I'm gonna get my tts working. We'll get the we'll get the donation stuff working
You know what's helping me out today. I am a cash app cult of psyche
You know, everything helps this week.
Appreciate it.
I'm gonna try to clean up a little bit.
Thanks for being here.
Thanks for, you know, being a little quiet.
It's always fun to at least talk to one person.
And I love you guys.
And, oh, okay, okay, okay.
And actually, oh yeah, so I'm gonna play
Food Sam's Favorite Song.
This is Food Sam's Favorite Song.
And even Black North likes it, and these guys are musicians, and so these are people that are like,
wow, this is catchy, because there's a lot of people that go,
welcome to the cold damn psyche. It's actually so good. So enjoy that, and I will see you later,
okay? I'm back. Love you.
A friendly face on every page
A laugh track floating through the haze
Everything feels safe these days
The neighbors wave, the children play
The sun shines bright, the bills get paid
A perfect house, a perfect street
A perfect smile, a perfect beat
It's the same
Another down the ceiling
Slowly just back down
And the beer's a blotting off